titlenine.com 2018-12-25

# Privacy & Security - Customer Support | Title Nine

## Your Privacy

Title Nine values our customers and respects your privacy. We collect information about you on our website in an effort to improve your shopping experience and to communicate with you about orders, services and products. This policy describes how we collect and use your personal information.

* * *

### What Personal Information does Title Nine collect?

When you place an order with us we collect your name, address, email address, telephone number and credit card information. If you ask to be placed on our email list, we will collect your name and email address.

In addition to personal information we may collect and use non-personally identifiable information (such as click behavior, browser type, time and date) during your visit to our websites and others to deliver more relevant advertising likely to be of greater interest to you. You may visit the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) and the [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/) to learn more about interest-based advertising or to opt out of receiving advertisements tailored to your interests on your browser from their participants. Note that electing to opt out will not prevent ads from appearing, but it may make the ads you see less relevant to your interests. We may also use technologies, such as cookies, to provide you with relevant online display advertising tailored to your interests. To opt out of our cookies used for this online advertising, [click here](http://dtmc.titlenine.com/adinfo/choice/prod/?type=fpc&cid=61618&cname=Title%20Nine&cmagic=65bb68&clogo=61618.png&loc=us&lang=en-us).

BACK TO TOP

* * *

### How do we use your email address?

We use your email to communicate all kinds of Customer Service information. We use your email to:

  * Send you immediate confirmation of your order
  * Send you confirmation when your order ships
  * Send you information when your backorder ships
  * Send you confirmation that we received your return

Additionally, we will notify you of new products and upcoming sales and events, such as web-only specials, speakers, book signings and events that are of interest to women involved with sports. What we DON'T use it for is anything else. We don't sell or rent your email address to anyone. No partners, no manufacturers, no other lists. No fooling.

BACK TO TOP

* * *

Your information is sometimes shared with vendors Title Nine has partnered with to process and ship your order. Sometimes we make your name and postal address available to other direct marketing companies who may have offers of interest to you. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please contact customer support. We use marketing consultants to help us maintain and analyze our data and allow us to mail our catalogs and market more efficiently. They may use cookies or web beacons to collect information about you, in connection with providing you information about products and services that might be of interest to you. You can learn more about this or choose not to have this information used by our trusted third party advertising partners.

BACK TO TOP

* * *

### How can you update your personal information?

If you are a registered user of our website, please login to your Account, then select “My Information” to modify your Account Information and Profile.

To change your email address with us, please contact us here and include your first and last name, your old email address and your new email address. 

BACK TO TOP

* * *

## Mailing Lists

### How do mailing lists work?

It's one of those unavoidable truths in the mail order business. We need to rent or exchange names with other like-minded businesses in order to stay in business and grow. What that means is, chances are, if our catalog just arrived out of nowhere in your mailbox, we probably rented your name from another company. Or we may have exchanged some of our buyers' names for some of another company's buyers' names.

BACK TO TOP

* * *

### How do I prevent my name from being exchanged with other companies?

If you would prefer for us not to exchange your name with other companies, please let us know. You can contact customer support, or write us at:

Mailing List Preferences   
Title Nine   
6201 Doyle Street   
Emeryville, CA 94608.

BACK TO TOP

* * *

### How do I stop receiving duplicate catalogs?

Please help us eliminate duplicate catalog mailings. If you are receiving more than one Title Nine catalog, please let us know. Just email us and we'll take care of it. Please include the "keycodes" and "customer numbers" listed on the back of the catalogs. Thanks for your help.

BACK TO TOP

* * *

### How do I get my name removed from your mailing list?

If you'd like your name removed from our mailing list, please let us know. You can change your mailing list preferences here, contact us, or write us at:

Mailing List Preferences   
Title Nine   
6201 Doyle Street   
Emeryville, CA 94608

If you would like to be added to the National Do Not Mail List, you can contact the Direct Marketing Association by sending a letter plus a $1 check or money order to:

DMA Mail Preference Service   
PO Box 643   
Carmel, NY 10512

Phone: 212.768.7277   

BACK TO TOP

* * *

### Do you share my email address too?

No. We absolutely don't. More answers under “How do we use your email address?

BACK TO TOP

* * *

### Where do I send change of email address information?

To let us know that you've changed your email address, please contact us.

BACK TO TOP

* * *

## Safety & Security

### Is it safe for me to shop online at titlenine.com?

Your online orders at Title Nine are just as safe as any other credit card purchase that you'll ever make. We use a sophisticated encryption technology to keep your credit card information safe while you're shopping online. So whether you're buying at a retail store, through a mail order catalog or online at Title Nine, your transactions will all have the same high standards for security.

At Title Nine we use SSL (Secure Socket Layering) 128 bit encryption to protect your information as it travels over the internet. We also hold a secure key, or digital certificate, through Digital Signature Trust. This key ensures that we are who we say we are and that any data exchanged online is protected from theft and tampering. Consumer protection laws protect you against any unauthorized use of your credit card. Federal law dictates that your legal liability is limited to $50 if your credit card number is used without your permission. If you suspect any illegal use of your card, call your issuing bank immediately to make sure your rights are protected.
